SURITA SPIGNER

in LinkedIn | M suspigner@gmail.com | Portfolio

Tools

- UX Research : Qualtrics | NVivo | Python | Power Automate | SurveyMonkey | Google Forms | Excel | Visio | Lucidchart
- UX Design: Figma | Sketch | Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, XD, InDesign, Photoshop) | Canva | CSS | HTML | GitHub
- Project Management: Smartsheet | SharePoint | Miro | Slack | Google Suite | Drive | Microsoft Teams Suite | Outlook

- UX Research | Mixed Method (Qualitative, Quantitative, User Research, Competitive, Scientific, Lean Six Sigma) | Testing (A/B, User, Usability, Preference) | Interview (Contextual Inquiry, Remote, Focus Group) | Survey | Analysis (Comparative, Competitive, Heuristic Evaluation, Affinity Diagram) Mapping (Workflow Architecture, Mind Map, Interaction Map, Voice Map, Process, Risk) | Persona | Data Visualization
- UX Design | User Experience (UX) | User Interaction (UI) | Visual | Flat Icon | Accessible | Multi-Platform (Mobile (iOS & Android), Web, Voice, Smart Device | Prototype (Interactive, Hi Fi, Responsive, Gesture, Rapid, Paper, Low Fi, Wireframe, Mockup) | UX Writing | Instruction
- Project Management | Research Management | Change | Risk | Lean Six Sigma | Agile | Waterfall | Cross-Disciplinary

UX Research & Design Consulting

UX Consultant Moorestown Library Moorestown, NJ 09/2019 - 01/2020

 Designed and conducted mixed-method user research resulting in nearly \$200K budget allocation improving technology resources, maintenance, and youth services. Interviewed community members, analyzed transcripts using NVivo coding over 350+ nodes, and delivered a community profile and solutions report.

NBC Universal Ann Arbor, MI 01/2019 - 06/2019 UX Consultant

• Alexa NBC-Skills App: Prototyped voice interactions for finance management. Led team of user researchers to illuminate millennial brand perception of the "Make It" platform and personal finance management needs using user interviews, surveys using Qualtrics, and user testing of voice interactions.

UX Consultant Ann Arbor, MI 01/2019 - 06/2019

- Drove accessibility & gesture improvements for CNBC iOs app by re-designing UI & video for Markets and Live TV pages using Photoshop and Illustrator.
- Designed and conducted UX research for CNBC's Emerging Platforms dept., including 3-level comparative competitor matrix, interaction maps with pain points, nearly 100 millennial surveys, and 1:1 user interviews & preference tests to identify gesture impulses.

UX Consultant Flovd Home Detroit, MI 09/2018 - 12/2019

 Project Manager and co-researcher on cross-disciplinary research team optimizing efficiency of start-up client by employing best practices for enterprise file sync & share system using contextual inquiry interviews, heuristic evaluation, & workflow maps to identify pain points using Lucidchart.

Experience

Informatics Project Manager

Washington State Department of Health

01/2021 - 12/2022 Seattle, WA

- Led dozens of technical & non-technical projects, delivering 110+ deliverables and maintaining a 100% success rate by creating advanced dashboard and tracking tools through Smartsheet, Sharepoint, Microsoft Teams Suite and Lean Six Sigma management methods.
- Managed enterprise projects including state emergency response infrastructure, developed programs including the Epidemiology Response Team Program, the Outbreak Response Coordination Program, the Surge Support Pilot Program, and the Project Prioritization Pipeline Program.
- Drove operational improvement by identifying 100+ risks and efficiency solutions and developing the agency's first-ever end-to-end visual and narrative workflows for electronic lab reporting, validation, and IT routing. Mapping over 250+ steps spanning 5 technical teams using Visio.
- Facilitated \$1M tech contractor transition with zero data loss. Developed a fully automated employee scheduling application, decreasing missed appointments by 100% and leveraging Power Automate, SharePoint, and Outlook to customize notifications & reservations.

User Experience Intern 06/2020 - 08/2020

- Multiple Award-winning mobile application: Identified & prototyped 45 highest user-valued features using Figma and Adobe Illustrator.
- Advanced the minimum viable product into high-fidelity prototypes through high-fidelity prototyping and user research (1,200+ data points collected across 200+ feature multi-matrix comparative analysis using advanced Excel, max-diff user preference survey, and preference analysis using Qualtrics).

Data Specialist **Neighborhood House** Seattle, WA 07/2017 - 09/2018

Outreach Coordinator

07/2016 - 07/2017

- Supervised data reporting for 5 public health & social services sites in King County increasing reporting performance record to 98% from 66% for quarterly, weekly, and yearly reporting. Created first-ever multi-database guidance using Adobe Creative Suite and facilitated employee database training.
- Led city-wide data collection & outreach including Most Steer Clear campaign, using Instagram & Facebook for social media advertising target & analysis.

Research & Advocacy Board Chair

North Seattle College

Seattle, WA

08/2012 - 06/2014

- Research & Advocacy Board Chair, North Seattle College: Supervised 6 paid staff. Enhanced hiring diversity through BIPOC, veteran, & ESL outreach.
- Managed qualitative & quantitative research across 3 college campuses using SurveyMonkey, focus groups, & direct advocacy to State Legislators.

Undergraduate Researcher

University of Washington

09/2016 - 08/2017

Designed and conducted biology research and experiments using scientific method and Python and Excel to correlate marine trends.

Education

Master of Science in Information: User Experience & Human Computer Interaction

University of Michigan

Ann Arbor, MI

Graduated with 3.9 GPA | Info-Lab Member | Design Clinic Member | MECC Environmental Planning Partner | Master Capstone: Family Traveler Smart TV & Mobile App

Bachelor of Science in Biology Minor in Chemistry

University of Washington

Seattle, WA

Graduated with 3.6 GPA | 2014 Women in Science & Engineering Scholar | 2x McCoy-Livingston Scholar | 21st Century Fellow | Honors Student Council | Robinson Scholar

Volunteering

- Data Equity Action Team Representative., Washington State Department of Health: Supported equitable race data guidance (08/2021-12/2021)
- Mentor & Tutor, Seattle MESA: Mentored and tutored underrepresented, minority, and economically at risk students in STEM (09/2016-06/2017)
- Executive Board, Global Visionaries: Defined board mission & strategy. Hospital & reforestation volunteer in Antigua, Guatemala (07/2010-06/2012)